The Sound of 007 is a documentary, music, tv movie
film directed by Mat Whitecross.
Pull back the curtain on the remarkable history of six decades of James Bond music,  from
Sean Connery’s Dr No through to Daniel Craig’s final outing in No Time to Die.
Self, played by Daniel Craig.
Self, played by Rami Malek.
Self, played by Naomie Harris.
Self, played by Sam Mendes.
Self, played by Hans Zimmer.
Self, played by Cary Joji Fukunaga.
The History of Sound is a 2025 period romance drama film directed by Oliver Hermanus, written by Ben
Shattuck, and based on a pair of his short stories: "The History of Sound" and "Origin Stories".
It follows the relationship between two men, Lionel (Paul Mescal) and David (Josh O'Connor), who meet in 1917 while attending the New England
Conservatory of Music, and after World War I travel together recording folk songs of their countrymen in rural Maine in the winter of 1920.
The film had its world premiere at the 2025 Cannes Film Festival on
May 21, where it was nominated for the Palme d'Or.
It was released in the United States by Mubi on September 12.